{
    "id": "4714e65b42294b54b6782807a96de3cf",
    "title": "Money Idioms",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "If these activists are really interested in eradicating poverty and malnutrition they must put their money where their …………………… is.",
            "description": "To put your money where your mouth is to practice what you preach.",
            "answers": [
                "hand",
                "mouth",
                "heart"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9db01043b93b4029be898b47ce98aa1e"
        },
        {
            "question": "He can buy just about anything he wants. His wife has got ……………………… of money.",
            "description": "Pots of money = lot of money",
            "answers": [
                "pots",
                "tins",
                "barrels"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b628ef9b17254ce5a5b61b00b6bc8343"
        },
        {
            "question": "He doesn’t have to work. He’s already got plenty of money to ……………………… around.",
            "description": "To throw money around is to spend it carelessly on unnecessary things.",
            "answers": [
                "kick",
                "fool",
                "throw"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "04750c22b08a4f199c935f5fe059f745"
        },
        {
            "question": "They hit pay ……………………………. with their new gaming app.",
            "description": "Hit pay dirt = Find something very profitable ",
            "answers": [
                "dirt",
                "packet",
                "smart"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9a32d3fd31354c70bb373022d356d204"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had to pay through the ………………………… to get my old car repaired.",
            "description": "To pay through the nose is to pay too much money for something.",
            "answers": [
                "ears",
                "eyes",
                "nose"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7d2c0c47991a4fbf874694a7baf5f6b3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Employers are paying ………………………. dollar to retain talent.",
            "description": "To pay top dollar is to pay a lot of money for something.",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "big",
                "top"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "500b767e03b044919e494e643874f774"
        },
        {
            "question": "That velvet gown cost me a …………………………..",
            "description": "When something costs you a pretty penny, it is very expensive.",
            "answers": [
                "pretty penny",
                "handsome penny",
                "hot penny"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b8287dfa0a574d97b6e800d4864f2127"
        },
        {
            "question": "She may be .......................................... poor, but she is honest.",
            "description": "Dirt poor = Extremely poor",
            "answers": [
                "dirt",
                "filth"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9cf6a1c626ff4e4c963d8230d24ade65"
        },
        {
            "question": "She may be as poor as a …………………………….., but she is content.",
            "description": "As poor as church mice = Very poor ",
            "answers": [
                "church mouse",
                "alley cat",
                "street dog"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "195ed6343fdf4b7cb952372e717802ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "He earns the money, but it is his wife who holds the ..............................................",
            "description": "To hold the purse strings = To hold the purse strings is to control a family’s or company’s money",
            "answers": [
                "purse strings",
                "wallet",
                "coffers"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b885d284689d4ab7bac817885e9a2e75"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ............................................ rich and that’s why he married her.",
            "description": "Filthy rich = Extremely rich",
            "answers": [
                "dirt",
                "dirty",
                "filthy"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2b1a1f28c5b242e3a89b7daed557211c"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can’t ...................................... Peter to pay Paul. If that is your policy you will never be out of debt.",
            "description": "Rob Peter to pay Paul = Borrow money from one person to pay back money borrowed from another person.",
            "answers": [
                "rob",
                "kidnap",
                "pawn"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0ab10c7a440d4252beeaa1282c20125e"
        }
    ]
}